export const pythonLoopControlAssignment = {
  title: 'Python Loop Control â€“ Assignment',
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'Which statement immediately terminates a loop?',
      options: ['continue', 'pass', 'break', 'stop'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'Which statement skips execution of remaining code in current iteration?',
      options: ['break', 'continue', 'pass', 'exit'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'Which statement is used as a placeholder?',
      options: ['break', 'continue', 'pass', 'return'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'break is mostly used to?',
      options: [
        'Skip iteration',
        'End loop',
        'Pause program',
        'Restart loop',
      ],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'continue statement works with?',
      options: ['If', 'Loop', 'Function', 'Class'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'Which statement avoids syntax error when no action is required?',
      options: ['break', 'continue', 'pass', 'none'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'Which is NOT a loop control statement?',
      options: ['break', 'continue', 'pass', 'print'],
      correctIndex: 3,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'Loop control improves?',
      options: ['Speed', 'Readability', 'Logic control', 'All'],
      correctIndex: 3,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'continue statement sends control to?',
      options: [
        'Loop start',
        'Loop condition check',
        'End of program',
        'Function',
      ],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'Loop control statements are mainly used in?',
      options: ['Data types', 'Loops', 'Functions', 'Input output'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
  ],
}